    const flashCards = [
        { question: "Q1 what are literals", answer: "constant values of immutable variables" },
        { question: "Q2 difference between primitive datatype and reference datatype", answer: "primitive: built-in types (int, double, char, bool) & hold values directly on stack \nnon-primitives/Reference: Object classes (String, Array, List) and hold addresses pointing at the value" },
        { question: "Q3 difference between do-while loop and while loop", answer: "do-while loop will run through the body (hehe) at least once before checking the condition. while loop checks the condition first" },
        { question: "Q4 what is JRE (not Joe Rogan Experience), and how to check if it's installed on your PC", answer: "Java runtime environment: runs Java programs, includes java libraries (similar to .NET Runtime), to check: java -version"},
        { question: "Q5 what is JDK, and how to check if it's installed on PC", answer: "Java development kit: Java compiler (similar to .NET SDK), to check: run javac -version"},
        { question: "Q6 what is JVM, what does it allow", answer: "Java virtual machine: it's integrated inside JDK and it converts Java into machine code (similar to CLR). it allows WORA write-once-run-anywhere"},
        { question: "Q7 can you have multiple main methods in a java project", answer: "you can have multiple main methods and each can be compiled individually, in contrast to C#, where there is a single entry point and project compiled as single assembly"},
        { question: "Q8 where can breakpoints be set?", answer: "at executable lines"},
        { question: "Q9 what the frick is wrong with this loop? \nwhile (windowType == null || windowType != \"g\" || windowType != \"t\")", answer: "infinite loop: if windowType is g than it naturally cannot be t. \ncorrect: (!windowType.equals(\"g\")) && !windowType.equals(\"t\") " },
        { question: "Q10 what is the default local hosting port for web development frameworks (react, springboot etc.)", answer: "EIGHTY EIGHTY 8080!!!"},
        { question: "Q11 while debugging, a line hightlighted in green means", answer: "next line to be executed."},
        { question: "Q12 difference between if and switch expressions", answer: "if conditions tested must be bool. switch can be any, it simply checks if the evaluated expression match any of the cases. switch also NEEDS a break and a default case"},
        { question: "Q13 use case difference between for and while loops", answer: " for when you know how many iterations. while when you don't know..duh"},
        { question: "Q14 difference between new Random(6967) and new Random()", answer: "the first one uses a seed value (6967) which is the id associated to a squence of random numbers. meaning everytime, we run the application, it will call the same sequence of numbers."},
        { question: "Q15 what are Heap and Stack", answer: "both areas of memory. Stack stores local variables and function call information, Heap stores Objects"},
        { question: "Q16 is a String immutable, what does immutability mean", answer: "not immutable, it means that once created in the memory it cannot be changed"},
        { question: "Q17 can you change a String from immutable to mutable", answer: "no, any modification like String string += 'value' creates another String"},
        { question: "Q18 what are StringBuilders", answer: "classes that modify Strings, used instead of modifying Strings directly. Can append, insert, delete without creating new objects"},
        { question: "Q19 difference between StringBuilders and StringBuffers", answer: "Builder is faster and single-threaded"},
        { question: "Q20 what are the types of exceptions", answer: "checked and unchecked. checked: validators created by coder to create exceptions using throws, occur at compiled time. unchecked: exceptions that do not need to be declared or caught, occur at runtime"},
        { question: "Q21 throw vs throws", answer: "Throw: method to throw a single exception object at a time. Throws: written in method signature stating that the method MIGHT throw an exception"},
        { question: "Q22 abstraction defrick is that", answer: "Process to hide implementation details, done through abstract classes and interface"},
        { question: "Q23 encapsulation defrick is that", answer: "Process to bundle fields and (get and set) methods. that way you can create response and validation to restrict direct access to the fields"},
        { question: "Q24 abstract class vs interface", answer: "abstract classes are skeleton classes with fields and virtual methods to be overriden by child classes. Interface are collections of methods without implementation. interface components don't rely on eachother, facilitate decoupling and can inherit multiple child classes. use abstract classes when you want default behaviour."},
        { question: "Q25 what is the properties file in springboot", answer: "config file for port number, verison info, database connection, environment variables, access keys"},
        { question: "Q26 what is good code", answer: "readable, maintainable. Readable: consistent conventions. Maintainable: Testable and with scalability in mind: separte layers (UI, API, DATABASE)."},
        { question: "Q27 what is polymorphism", answer: "same method call can behave differently depending on object. Done through overloading and overriding"},
        { question: "Q28 what is overloading and overriding", answer: "Overloading: same method name, different parameters using constructors. Overriding: subclass provides its own overriden method to parent classe's method (virtual method in C# term)"},
        { question: "Q29 which expression skips processing the remainder of the code in its block in it's current iteration", answer: "continue"},
        { question: "Q30 what does the static keyword mean", answer: "this method belong to the class itself, not an object. can't initialize it"},
        { question: "Q31 what is the package keyword", answer: "declares a namespace. put it on top of a java file along with all the immigrants"},
        { question: "Q32 what is delegation", answer: "it's the process of separating functions that do separate things to different classes"},
        { question: "Q33 what are properties, accessors and mutators", answer: "properties in java isn't quite the same as in C# it simply refers to the fields. but conceptually both languages do the same things (use getters and setters aka accessors and mutators) to access and modify fields."},
        { question: "Q34 what is this", answer: "keyword to refer to current object. used to distinguish an object's field from a method parameter. example: this.age = age assigning field = parameter"},
        { question: "Q35 can you use   this   in a static method", answer: "Nahh cuz static methods can't be instantiated"},
        { question: "Q36 what are constructors and why use them", answer: "method to initialize properties (fields) of an object. must have same name as its class. no return type. used to ensure objects are initialized in a valid state"},
        { question: "Q37 what is dependency injection,", answer: "design pattern that provides required objects to a class through constructors, methods, or container, rather than instantiating them internally. Makes the code easier to read, test and scale."},
        { question: "Q38 composition vs inheritance.", answer: "inheritance extends a parent class. Composition contains (implements) another class."},
        { question: "Q39 what is @Override annotation. and what are annotations", answer: "Annotations are metadata for compiler to run error checks both at compile and runtime. @Override tells compiler a method overrides or implements a parent/interface method."},
        { question: "Q40 implements vs extends keywords", answer: "implements: used when implement interface methods. extends: used when declaring interface, it can inherit from other classes/interfaces."},
        { question: "Q41 how do you call a static method of an interface if possible", answer: "interfaces CAN have static/default method implementation. you can call it by using the interface name directly (without creating an object cuz you can't) and a dot operator"},
        { question: "Q42 what is data marshalling and unmarshalling howwdy", answer: "marshalling: object -> data, unmarshalling is the inverse. data form could mean html, json etc."},
        { question: "Q43 what is does the PrintWriter class do and what is the flush() method", answer: "PrintWriter writes output to file or stream. When you write data to a file/stream, they are not immediately written, they are sent to a buffer. flush() writes any buffered output to the file"},
        { question: "Q44 what is SDLC", answer: "Software Development Life cycle: composed of different models.. waterfall.. iterative.. Agile"}
        // ...more questions and answers here
    ];
